《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
看看你茂密的胸毛
Oh, look at all that chest hair.
和小龅牙
And overbite.
完全就是沃罗威茨家族的一员呀
Of course you're a Wolowitz.
我勒个去  他咬了我
Son of a bitch, he bit me.
我还是去自己急诊室确认一下吧
Okay, I guess I'll just go to the emergency room to be safe.
华仔  这只是你的臆想病犯了
Howie, this is just your hypochondria.
我坐到静音键上  以为自己聋了
When I sat on the mute button and thought I'd gone deaf,
那才叫臆想病
that was my hypochondria.
我们另找个时间告诉他我怀孕了吧
We'll find another time to tell him I'm pregnant.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
"我们"
"We"?
这是什么
What is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许后面写了什么吧
Maybe it says something on the back.
"后续提示  请看牛奶盒"
"Continued on milk."
如果你是想骗我自己做早饭
If you're tricking me into making my own breakfast,
我妈从前没成功  你也别想得逞
it didn't work for my mom, and it won't work for you.
"是"
"Are."
"我们是"
"We are..."
"预知后事  请看勺子"
"See spoons for more."
会是什么呢
What could it be?
"我们是格鲁特"
"We are Groot"?
"我们是冠军"
"We are the champions"?
"我们是一家人"
"We are family"?
"我永远同我的姐妹们在一起"
"I got all my sisters with me."
你是说真的吗
Are you serious?
是的
Yeah.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
确定一定以及肯定[阳性]
Pretty positive.
这是个双关语笑话  因为怀孕测试也是...
That's a joke, because the pregnancy test says...
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
太棒了
This is incredible.
我们要当爸爸妈妈了
We're gonna be parents?
以后我们可以优先上飞机了
We're gonna get to board planes first.
终于可以看看
Finally gonna get to see
商场的家庭卫生间长什么样子了
what's in that family bathroom at the mall.
我知道  这事太疯狂了
I know, it's crazy.
简直超乎想象
It is crazy.
这种事情该如何准备呢
I mean, how do you... prepare for something like this?
我都不确定自己以前抱过婴儿没有
I'm not even sure I've held a baby before.
没关系  你会慢慢学会的
Oh, it's okay, you'll figure it out.
可还有其他的事呢
But how's this all gonna work?
我们需要找保姆吗
Do we get a nanny?
我是说  我们请得起保姆吗
I mean, can we afford a nanny?
就算请得起  也不能找漂亮的
And if we can, we can't get a pretty one,
否则我们的婚姻就会出现危机
'cause it'll wreck our marriage.
但也不能找太丑的  否则会吓坏宝宝的
We can't get an ugly one, 'cause it'll scare the kid.
我不知道  华仔
I-I don't know, Howie.
我们这里算是好学区吗
Are we in a good school district?
你信天主教  我是犹太人
You're Catholic, I'm Jewish.
我们的孩子应该信什么教呢
What religion do we raise it?
如果生了男孩  应该让他行割礼吗
And if it's a boy, do we get him circumcised?
有人说割礼是野蛮的行为
People say it's barbaric,
但如果不割  看起来又像面包裹腊肠
but if we don't, it looks like a pig in a blanket.
冷静一下  一切都会好的
Calm down, it's gonna be okay.
怎么可能会好
How's it gonna be okay?
你看看我  我整个人一团糟
Look at me, I'm a mess.
这就表示这孩子会是半团糟
And that means this baby's gonna half a mess.
孩子早就输在起跑线上了
And that's even before we screw it up
加上保姆廉价长相一般就更惨了
with our cut-rate moderately attractive nanny.
拉杰  我看新闻说你们学院的一群人
Hey, Raj, I read a couple guys in your department
好像在太阳系发现了新的行星
may have discovered a new planet in our solar system?
我也听说了
Oh, I heard about that.
怎么不是你发现的呢
Why didn't you discover it?
因为我没有泡在望远镜室里
Because instead of being in the telescope room,
而是忙着给你们几个做节日手工果酱
I was busy making you guys homemade jam for the holidays.
当你凭借波森莓果酱
Well, you be sure to let us know
赢得诺贝尔奖时  记得通知我们
when you win the Nobel Prize for boysenberry.
-大家好  -你好啊
- Hello. - Hey, bud.
你准备好就能开玩了
Ready to play when you are.
先等一等
Yeah, um, in a minute.
我有事要告诉你们
I actually need to tell you guys something.
如果是为了12月的手工果酱说谢谢
If it's "Thank you" for the homemade jam you got in December,
恭喜你  你是第一个这么做的人
congratulations, you're the first one.
出什么事了
What's going on?
那个  我...
I'm, uh...
要当爸爸了
uh, gonna be a father.
-太棒了  -什么  恭喜你
- That's so amazing. - What? Congratulations.
太糟了
Oh, no.
你干嘛说太糟了
Why "Oh, no"?
因为所有的事都要改变了
Because this changes everything.
咱们以后的漫画之夜怎么办
What about comic book night?
我们还能愉快地一起打游戏吗
Uh, what about playing games together?
我们还能一起去迪斯尼乐园吗
What about our trips to Disneyland?
以后有了孩子  我们还怎么做这些事呀
How can we do those things with a child around?
别紧张  我们大家可以忍受两个小宝宝
Relax, there's room for two babies in this group.
我勒个去
Oh, dear Lord...
佩妮也怀孕了吗
Penny's pregnant, too?
另一个宝宝就是你
You're the other baby.
真的吗
Oh, really?
有哪个宝宝每隔11天就需要刮一次胡子啊
Okay, well, would a baby have to shave once every 11 days?
有哪个成年人会拒绝吃他的全麦饼干
Would an adult refuse to eat his graham crackers
仅仅因为其中一块破掉了吗
because one of them was broken?
这局我们俩平手
I guess we'll call this a draw.
我很高兴你们俩都在这里
So, I'm glad you guys are here.
有件事我要告诉你们
There's something I want to share with you.
华仔和我要...
Howie and I are going to...
莱纳德说你怀孕了
Leonard says you're pregnant.
什么
What?
"不要说出来
"Don't say anything.
她告诉你时要装成很惊讶的样子"
Act surprised when she tells you."
好吧  你想我们怎么演
All right, how you want to do this?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我的天  我真不敢相信
Oh, my God, I can't believe it!
太激动人心了
This is so exciting!
是呀  是挺让人激动的
Yeah, it's all real exciting.
你  你不开心吗
Are-are you not happy about this?
开心呀  我当然开心
I am. Of-of course I am. I'm...
可能只是荷尔蒙作祟吧
I'm sure it's just the hormones.
但还是很奇怪
But it's weird--
华仔这么多年来一直想要小孩
Howie's the one who's been talking about having kids for years,
我本来很开心地告诉他
and I was all excited to tell him
以为他会激动到疯掉
because I thought he'd be thrilled,
结果他慌成一团
but then he started to flip out
搞得我现在觉得这不是好事
and now this feels like a bad idea
而且我还会变胖
and I'm gonna get fat.
不  不  别这样  你不会变胖
No, no, come on. Come on, you're not gonna get fat.
你只会越来越美  焕发母性的光辉
You're gonna be beautiful and glowing
变成最性感最可爱的孕妈宝贝
and-and have the cutest little baby bump ever.
你说起来倒容易  你个瘦皮猴
Easy for you to say, skinny bitch.
抱歉  都是荷尔蒙作祟
Sorry, hormones.
没关系  我只听到了"瘦"这个字
Oh, that's all right. All I heard was "skinny."
虽然霍华德的表现和你想象的不一样
I wouldn't make too much out of Howard
但我觉得你不用担心
not reacting the way you expected him to.
没错  他只是一开始有点被吓到了
Yeah, I'm sure it was just the initial shock of it all.
你们说得对
You're probably right.
我们好好谈过之后  他开始平静下来了
After we talked about it, he started to calm down.
我就不该养孩子
I shouldn't be raising a kid.
我自己都不爱吃蔬菜
I don't even eat my own vegetables.
老兄  你可能反应过度了
Buddy, I-I think you might be overreacting.
还有我这个鼻子
And then there's this nose.
如果他长得像我怎么办
I mean, what if he looks like me?
更糟糕的是...
Or worse...
如果女儿长得像我怎么办
what if she looks like me?
更别提对我们这个社交圈子的影响了
Not to mention the impact on our social circle.
所有一切都会随之改变
Everything's going to change.
霍华德不能像以前那样频繁地过来了
Howard won't be able to come over as much.
他也可以把孩子带来呀
Well, he could bring the baby here.
但那样的话  我们就得给公寓装上婴儿保护了
Oh, but then we'd have to baby-proof the apartment.
我姐姐的厕所里就有那么一个马桶锁
You know, my sister has one of those toilet locks in her bathroom.
我拥有双博士学位  都只能憋屈尿洗手池里
I have two doctorates, I still had to go in the sink.
天啊  你们知不知道
Oh, my God, and do you have any idea
养一个孩子有多费钱啊
how expensive having a kid is?
有人写过  在洛杉矶养一个孩子到念完大学
I read that in Los Angeles, raising a child through college
费用超过一百万美元
can cost over a million dollars.
一百万美元
A million dollars?
不行了  感觉我蛋蛋相攻  蛋疼不已
God, it's like my nuts just kicked me in the nuts.
好的  我懂了
That's it-- I got to start
我要现在就开始多赚钱
earning more money right now.
我知道了  你可以跟伯纳黛特申请
I know-- you could ask Bernadette
让她多给你点零花钱
for a raise in your allowance.
这不是玩笑
This isn't a joke.
我没开玩笑
I wasn't joking.
船到桥头自然直
It'll be fine.
天天都有人生孩子
People have kids every day.
你会想到办法的
You'll figure this out.
就是  别这样
Yeah, come on,
你也知道  这是大好的消息
this is great news and you know it.
你说得对  我只是
You're right, it is, I'm just...
一时有些接受不了
A little overwhelmed right now.
知道我们该去干嘛吗
Hey, you know what we should do?
全体去做输精管切除术  以免后患吗
All get vasectomies so this doesn't happen to us?
一起出去庆祝
Go out and celebrate.
刚才不是你说过最差的主意
But not your worst idea.
我们一起去放松放松心情吧
Hey, let's go do something to get your mind off this.
好啊  我们应该出去
Yeah, yeah, we should go out.
去哪
Where?
不知道  酒吧
Uh, I don't know, a bar?
不能喝酒
Can't drink.
我们能喝  但好吧
We can, but all right.
你饿吗  要不要去你喜欢的那家寿司店
Are you hungry? How about that sushi place you love?
医生说我不能吃寿司
Doctor said I can't have sushi.
好的  我们也可以哪都不去
Okay, look, we don't have to go anywhere.
我们可以就待在这  在浴缸里聊天
We can just, you know, stay here and hang out in the hot tub.
医生说我不能泡浴缸
Doctor said I can't go in the hot tub.
要不你还是换个医生吧
Maybe you should get a new doctor.
干嘛  他也说了你不能笑吗
What, he said you can't laugh either?
让我们举杯敬我们的朋友  霍华德
I'd like to propose a toast to our friend, Howard--
一个胸怀宽广  灵魂美丽
his, um, his big heart, his beautiful soul...
穿着勒蛋小紧裤
And his tight little pants
也没有因此不育的男人
that somehow did not make him sterile.
干杯
Cheers.
看这个
Well, look at this.
发明这个小雨伞的人
I bet whoever invented tiny umbrellas
估计是不用担心没钱了
doesn't have to worry about money.
他想生几个孩子就生几个
He can have all the kids he wants.
还能挡掉头顶的一小部分区域的雨滴
And can keep a small portion of their heads dry.
如果我要养这个孩子
If I'm gonna have any chance of raising this kid,
必须想出超级赚钱的点子
I need to come up with a big idea to make some money.
没理由不行啊
There's no reason you can't.
你说得倒容易
That's easy for you to say.
你和谢尔顿已经想出了超流氦模型
You and Sheldon already came up with your superfluid helium model.
那只是研究
That's just research.
根本没机会用来赚钱
We're never gonna make any money from it.
去他的氦  这杯子里的旁趣酒
Forget helium. The real superfluid
才是真正的超流逼
is the fruit punch in this mug.
让我想起我爸的秘密
Reminds me of my daddy's secret
"不许告诉妈妈"果汁
"Don't Tell Mama" juice.
这酒挺烈的  你慢点喝
Uh, these are strong, you should slow down.
那我再喝最后一口
I'll just take one last sip.
好吧  这个发明怎么样
Okay, how about this for an invention--
稍微大一点的鸡尾酒小雨伞
slightly... bigger cocktail umbrellas.
这算什么新发明
How is that a new invention?
我不知道  苹果公司也只是产品大小变换
I don't know, all Apple does is change the size of things
我们不也买个不停吗
and we keep buying them.
真的  我对我的大iPad
It's true. I like my giant iPad
和我的小iPad的喜爱
and my little iPad
几乎等同于我对正常尺寸iPad的喜爱
almost as much as my regular-sized iPad.
这个地方太棒了
This place is terrific.
我们之前怎么没来过
Why-why have we never been here before?
跟其他好玩却不能做的事一样  因为你啊
The same reason we don't do a lot of fun stuff-- you.
挺伶牙俐齿  牙尖嘴利
That's some smart talk from a guy
就是脸上焦距老跑掉啊
who can't even keep his face in focus.
厕所在哪
Where's the bathroom?
-在拐角处  -失陪
- Uh, it's in the corner. - Excuse me.
你们好呀
Hey, how you doin'?
希望男女厕标识明显一点
I hope the bathroom is clearly marked.
无所谓  反正他是往厨房方向走去了
Doesn't matter. He's headed for the kitchen anyway.
这个主意也许行
Maybe that's an idea--
给醉酒人士的导向系统
guidance systems for drunk people.
早有了  叫优步叫车
They have that. It's called Uber.
在你的过冷氦试验中
In your supercooled helium experiments,
创建过量子漩涡吗
did you create quantum vortices?
有  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
如果你建立一个导向系统
Well, if you made a guidance system,
是不是可以把漩涡当做螺旋仪使用
couldn't you use those vortices as a gyroscope?
我从来没想过
I've never thought about that.
而且由于是在量子态下
And since it's in a quantum state,
就能保持无限持续
it would maintain an infinite persistence.
开创性启示  热带鸡尾酒
Groundbreaking revelations, tropical drinks.
这简直是最棒的一集
Tell me this isn't like the
《欲望都市》了
best episode of Sex and the City.
你真有可能想出了好点子
You may have actually just come up with something.
-你觉得是吗  -真的
- You think so? - I really do.
大伙  这里的厕所太妙了
You guys, the bathroom here is amazing.
里面有人在做饭呢
There's people cooking in it.
想想你有孩子后  有各种好玩的事可做
Think about all the fun things you get to do when you have a baby.
对呀
Yeah!
你可以买玩具和小衣服
Yeah, you get to buy toys and little clothes.
这些都给华仔做过了
I kind of already do that for Howie.
还有你只要饿了
And-and whenever you're hungry,
就会发现自己车上满地都有零食吃
you'll be in a minivan with Cheerios all over the floor.
我还给谢尔顿找到了个新旅行杯
Oh, and I just found a new travel cup for Sheldon.
一次只会出三颗零食
It only lets out three at a time.
你们是什么时候决定要孩子的
So, when did you guys decide to get pregnant?
我们不是决定的
Well, we didn't exactly decide.
我们聊过要孩子的事
We were talking about it,
然后有一天晚上就大胆疯了一下
and then one night we got a little reckless.
-给我们讲讲  -对  讲讲
- Oh, tell us! - Yeah, tell us.
不要啦  好丢脸哦
No, I'm embarrassed.
说吧  我们都是成人了
Oh, come on, we're all grown-ups.
-都有经验的  -我我我  有经验
- We've all done it. - Me! Me-me, too!
我是成人  做过了
I'm a grown-up and I've done it!
好吧
Fine.
那天我们在外面
We were out one night,
然后突然来了兴致
and things got a little spontaneous.
一听就知道内容很精彩
Oh, that sounds juicy.
当时谢尔顿没完没了地说时区和铁路安排
Well, Sheldon was going on and on about time zones
然后我就出去了...
and railroad schedules, and I went out...
等等  这事我记得  慢着
Wait, I remember that. Hang on.
你们是在我们家搞的吗
You did it at our place?
好像还是在谢尔顿床上
Kind of on Sheldon's bed.
-什么  -不
- What?! - No!
我想去厕所
I was headed to the bathroom,
碰到华仔从里面出来
and I passed Howie on his way out.
通常他会说"别进  进去会臭死"
Usually he says, "Do not go in there,"
但这次他说"我们进去吧"
but this time he said, "Hey, let's go in here."
你们怎么能这样
How could you do that?
对不起
I'm sorry,
但你也知道  跟自己的男人在一起
but you know what it's like when you're with your man
很容易情不自禁
and one thing leads to another.
这感觉姐知道  姐倍儿清楚
I do know what that's like. I really do.
我没找到任何人
I'm not seeing anyone
是这样使用液态氦漩涡
using liquid helium vortices like this.
我也没找到
I'm not finding anything either.
这是好事
That's a good sign.
等等  我找到点东西
Oh, wait, I found something.
该死  是什么
Damn. What is it?
这个视频  熊猫宝宝打喷嚏
This video. The baby panda sneezes,
把熊猫妈妈吓了一大跳
and the mama panda gets so scared.
能不能不跑题聊正事
Can you focus on what we're talking about?
好吧
All right.
听着  也许说的是酒话
Look, now, this may be the rum talking,
但如果漩涡释放率
but as long as the unpinning rate of the vortices
能保持在1.1到1.3
is kept within 1.1 and 1.3,
马格努斯力的问题就可以忽略不计
the Magnus force issue should be negligible.
他喝醉都比我们仨更聪明
Even drunk, he's still smarter than all of us.
还更壮
And stronger.
谁想看我去痛扁酒保一顿
Yeah. Who wants to see me beat up the bartender?
我拭目以待
I'd enjoy that.
放她一马吧  她是个好姑娘
Nah, she's a good kid.
如果真可行  我们可以去申请专利
If this is a viable thing, we could get a patent
然后授权给做导向系统的公司
and license it to companies that make guidance systems.
瞧  你知道要当爹的消息
Look at that. You've known you're gonna be a father
才不到一天你就已经雄起了
for less than a day and you're already stepping up.
相信我  你绝对能行
I'm telling you, you got this.
或许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
他当然对啦
Of course he's right.
你跟我最清楚小时候没爹疼有多惨
You and I both know how hard it is growing up without a father.
所以我十分确信
That's why I'm confident you're gonna be
你会尽力成为最好的爸爸
the best dad you can be.
谢谢你  谢尔顿
Thank you, Sheldon.
不客气
You're welcome.
如果是生了双胞胎
And if he has twins, we can do
我们就能拿来做好多屌爆的实验
all kinds of neat experiments on them.
你们想泡就泡吧
You guys can go in if you want.
我们要同进退
No, we're a team.
你不能泡  我们也不泡
If you can't go in, we're not going in.
那我们俩为什么还喝酒
Then why are we drinking?
她又不是怀上帝之子  不用这么牺牲吧
Okay, it's not like she's got the Christ child in there, all right?
是莱纳德
Oh. It's Leonard.
他说谢尔顿喝醉了  还说如果有兴趣
He says Sheldon's drunk and they're gonna do karaoke
欢迎加入他们唱卡拉ok
if we want to join them.
听起来挺有意思
That sounds fun.
惨了
Oh, no.
谢尔顿醉后乱发我短信了
Sheldon's drunk texting me.
写了什么
What's it say?
"要来跟我们一起唱歌吗"
"Would you like to sing karaoke with us."
这哪里算醉后乱发啊
How is that a drunk text?
问句他不用问号  而是句号
He used a period instead of a question mark.
他真是喝大了
He's so wasted.
♪ 爱片上映  那就走起 ♪
♪ Your movie's showing, so you're going ♪
♪ 票钱五块  甩都不甩 ♪
♪ Could care less about the five you're blowing ♪
♪ 影院变暗  好戏上演 ♪
♪ Theater gets dark just to start the show ♪
♪ 发现同排  有位美女 ♪
♪ You spot a fine woman sitting in your row, ♪
♪ 身穿黄衣 ♪
♪ she's dressed in yellow ♪
♪ 她说"你好" ♪
♪ She says, "Hello" ♪
♪ "帅哥坐我旁边可好" ♪
♪ "Come sit next to me, you fine fellow" ♪
♪ 一个飞身  你冲过去 ♪
♪ You run over there without a second to lose ♪
♪ 后续如何 ♪
♪ And what comes next, hey ♪
♪ 出招开泡 ♪
♪ Bust a move ♪
♪ 你若想要 ♪
♪ You want it ♪
♪ 就能得到  你若想要 ♪
♪ You got it, oh, you want it ♪
♪ 宝贝  你能搞定 ♪
♪ Baby, you got it ♪
♪ 出招开泡 ♪
♪ Just bust a move ♪
♪ 你若想要 ♪
♪ You want it ♪
♪ 就能得到 ♪
♪ You got it, oh ♪
♪ 你若想要  宝贝  就能得到 ♪
♪ You want it, baby, you got it ♪
♪ 出招开泡 ♪
♪ Just bust a move ♪
♪ 你若想要  宝贝  就能得到 ♪
♪ You want it, baby, you got it ♪
♪ 你若想要 ♪
♪ You want it ♪
男生们  恭喜你啊
Hey, guys. Congratulations!
谢谢
Thank you.
你还好吗
Hi. How are you doing?
好到不行
Oh, wonderful.
我正受音乐鼓舞来"出招开泡"呢
I'm being musically encouraged to bust a move.
如果我能懂那词是啥意思  我肯定做
If I knew what that meant, I might just do it.
我很庆幸你来了
I'm really glad you're here.
-我们能说两句吗  -可以
- Can we talk? - Sure.
等会你要上去唱吗
So, you gonna get up there later?
一只麦克风
A microphone,
一个模仿波利尼西亚宗教但错误百出的场地
a room full of inaccurate depictions of Polynesian religion,
一群想跑也跑不了的听众
and a captive audience to hear about it?
我绝对得去唱啊
You bet I am.
抱歉我今早那样惊慌失措
I'm sorry I freaked out this morning.
我想告诉你
I want you to know...
我不会再害怕了
I'm done being scared.
紧张没事啊  我也紧张
It's okay to be nervous. I am, too.
谢天谢地  我刚才全是胡扯  我觉得你可能
Thank God, 'cause I was lying-- you might not have to wait
不用等九个月就能看到有人拉屎尿在裤子里
nine months to see someone soil their pants.
但我也真心很兴奋
But I'm also really excited.
真心的
I mean it.
我也是
Me, too.
我爱你
I love you.
我会说这些话
And I'm not just saying that
绝对不是因为你的胸也会变大
because your breasts are gonna get bigger.
♪ 我们是恋人吗  女孩你别玩了 ♪
♪ Are we an item? Girl, quit playin' ♪
♪ 我们只是朋友 ♪
♪ We're just friends ♪
♪ 你说这什么话 ♪
♪ What are you sayin'? ♪
♪ 看着我的眼睛  说你爱着别人 ♪
♪ Say there's another and look right in my eyes ♪
♪ 我的初恋情人  让我初次心碎 ♪
♪ My first love broke my heart for the first time ♪
♪ 我当时就说了 ♪
♪ And I was like ♪
♪ 宝宝  宝宝  宝宝 ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby, ooh ♪
♪ 宝宝  宝宝  宝宝  别啊 ♪
♪ Like, baby, baby, baby, no ♪
♪ 宝宝  宝宝  宝宝 ♪
♪Like, baby, baby, baby, ooh ♪
♪ 我曾以为你只专属我一人 ♪
♪ I thought you'd always be mine ♪
♪ 宝宝  我需要你的爱 ♪
♪ Baby, I need your lovin', ♪
♪ 必须得到你全部的爱 ♪
♪ Got To have all your lovin' ♪
♪ 宝宝  我需要你的爱 ♪
♪ Baby, I need your lovin', ♪
♪ 必须得到你全部的爱 ♪
♪ Got To have all your lovin' ♪
♪ 宝宝  宝宝 ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ 宝宝  宝宝 ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby ♪
♪ Baby, baby ♪
♪ 啊  顶[使劲] ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
谢谢你们献唱  但我真的...
I appreciate this, but you really...
♪ 好好顶啊[使劲全力] ♪
♪ Push it real good ♪
♪ 祖宗之所埋骨 ♪
♪ Land where my fathers died ♪
♪ 先民之所夸张 ♪
♪ Land of the pilgrims' pride ♪
♪ 群山之隈相低昂 ♪
♪ From ev'ry mountainside ♪
♪ 自由之歌 ♪
♪ Let freedom ♪
♪ 声抑扬 ♪
♪ Ring... ♪
我想把我今晚
I'd like to dedicate
最后一首歌献给我的妻子
my last song of the evening to my wife,
兼死党
best friend, and...
现在还兼我孩子的妈
now the mother of our child.
我爱你  妮妮
I love you, Bernie.
♪ 怀着我的骨肉 ♪
♪ Havin' my baby ♪
♪ 用这种美妙的方式 ♪
♪ What a lovely way of sayin' ♪
♪ 表达你有多爱我 ♪
♪ How much you love me ♪
♪ 怀着我的骨肉 ♪
♪ Havin' my baby ♪
♪ 用这种美妙的方式 ♪
♪ What a lovely way of sayin' ♪
♪ 表达你会想着我 ♪
♪ Of sayin' what you're thinkin' of me ♪
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding!
什么样的疯子会在别人房里交媾啊
What kind of maniacs have coitus in someone else's bedroom?!
谢谢  帕萨迪纳市  晚安
Thank you, Pasadena! Good night!
昨晚真是太好玩了
That was such a fun night.
因为你能看到你的男人
Probably 'cause you got to see your man
掌握全场的模样
up there rockin' the mic.
是啊是啊  我当时还挺惊讶
Yeah, yeah. I was a little surprised
你居然决定要来一段口技表演
when you decided to beat-box.
其实我是哮喘犯了
That was really an asthma attack.
只是掩饰特别好
I just sold it.
我好为霍华德与伯纳黛特开心
Well, I am so happy for Howard and Bernadette.
我也是
Me, too.
那你想过吗
So, you ever think about it?
孩子吗
Babies?
现在不急  但未来某天肯定会要啊
Well, I'm not in a rush but someday, yeah, sure.
你呢
What about you?
我觉得我们一定会是很棒的父母
I think we'd make amazing parents.
你们说话能不能小声点
Will you guys keep it down?
另一方面  我们在某些地方还不够成熟
On the other hand, we might lack a certain maturity.